{
    "id": "5fbc0b647ca343e7a872f24ca79c2467",
    "title": "Adjectives: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "37872b073b53425d91073352aa11958d",
            "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The car sustained .................................................. damage in the accident.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "heavy",
                        "heavily",
                        "heavier"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................................. dog has his day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Every",
                        "All"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a man of ......................................... words.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... answer is quite right.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Neither",
                        "Both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The way was long, the wind was ..............................................., the minstrel was infirm and old.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cold",
                        "colder",
                        "coldly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "John won ............................................. prize in the quiz competition.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "first",
                        "the first"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy stood on the .................................... deck.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "burn",
                        "burning",
                        "burned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "King Francis was a ......................................... king and loved a royal sport.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hearty",
                        "heartily"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a ....................................... fellow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "brave",
                        "braver",
                        "bravely"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "In the furrowed land stood the ..................................... oxen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "patient",
                        "patience"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}